[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The expression social butterfly is often used to describe a woman. It means that she does this.", "correct_answer": "Flits from one person to another", "incorrect_answers": ["Uses too much cosmetics", "Behaves quite self-conceited", "Wears clothes with bright colors"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of food is the popular Arab dish called baklava?", "correct_answer": "Dessert", "incorrect_answers": ["Baked lamb", "Soup", "Stew"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these nicknames has been given to the U.S. state of Colorado?", "correct_answer": "Switzerland of America", "incorrect_answers": ["Sweden of America", "Himalayas of America", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Vampire bats can be quite tame, and even friendly to humans.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are the colors on the flag of  The Bronx, NY?", "correct_answer": "Blue, White, Orange", "incorrect_answers": ["Red, White, Blue", "Blue, White, Green", "Red, Green, Orange"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This extremely expensive 2004 movie directed by Oliver Stone barely managed to cover its enormous production costs.", "correct_answer": "Alexander", "incorrect_answers": ["Oceans Twelve", "World Trade Center", "Troy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of the following national costumes is not Chinese?", "correct_answer": "Kente cloth", "incorrect_answers": ["Qipao", "Cheongsam", "Mao suit"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the character voiced by Michelle Pfeiffer in the 1998 Academy Award-winning animated movie The Prince of Egypt?", "correct_answer": "Tzipporah", "incorrect_answers": ["Miriam", "Ruth", "Queen Tuya"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following actors did not appear in the 1988 Comedy, Earth Girls Are Easy?", "correct_answer": "Rick Moranis", "incorrect_answers": ["Jeff Goldblum", "Geena Davis", "Jim Carrey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Jane Addams is the founder of this movement in the United States.", "correct_answer": "Settlement House movement", "incorrect_answers": ["Womens Rights movement", "All of these", "Womens Liberation movement"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How did Leonardo DiCaprio express his care for the environment?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["By driving a hybrid car", "By installing solar panels on the roof of his house", "By flying on commercial flights instead of chartering private jets"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Michael Jackson---", "correct_answer": "wrote the book - The World of Beer.", "incorrect_answers": ["developed the moonwalk immediately after consuming 2 six packs of Michelob.", "All of these.", "is President of Denmarks Tuborg brewery."]}]